# **Daniel Romero Hernandez**

Madrid, Spain · +34 640 81 50 89 · da.romero.hernandez@gmail.com · Linkedin · Github

Extensive experience as a **Full Stack Developer**. Dedicated to overcoming challenges and delivering effective solutions to drive company success. Motivated to learn new skills.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Golden Soft Madrid, Spain

Full stack developer

Oct. 2022 - Oct. 2023

- Worked on a .NET desktop application responsible for managing and accounting across +1000 companies.
- Enhanced my ability to analyze and restructure +11 years code, improving its readability and maintainability.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to enhance system performance and drive continuous improvement initiatives.

JdeRobot academy Madrid, Spain

Full stack developer

Jan. 2022 - Sep. 2022

- Developed an open source Django web platform featuring Robotics and Computer Vision courses.
- Strengthened team organization skills through effective Git workflow and Trello task management.

# **PROJECTS**

# **Gym Pilot**

Web and mobile app for recording workouts and reviewing statistics.

- Developed with Next.js (React framework) using Typescript and Tailwind CSS.
- Built the back-end API using the Django REST Framework (Python), and implemented user authentication and authorization systems, including Google OAuth and JWT.
- Designed and implemented the database using PostgreSQL.
- Deployed to production with **AWS EC2** and **Nginx**.
- Implemented CI/CD pipelines using **Docker Compose** for streamlined deployment.

### **Profit Pilot**

Web app for tracking expenses and increasing your savings.

- Created using **Django** with **MySQL** as the database.
- Deployed to production with AWS EC2 and Nginx.
- Employed **GitHub** for managing version control.

#### **EDUCATION**

Mastermind Madrid, Spain

Advanced software and hardware courses

Nov. 2023 - Jan. 2024

- Worked with **Linux** OS developing skills in networking and computer hardware.
- Gained proficiency in **Docker** and server deployment techniques.

# **Rey Juan Carlos University**

Madrid, Spain

Bachelor's degree in Game Development

2018 - 2022

Acquired expertise in video game programming and multiplayer server management.